http://www.columbussymphony.com/about/privacy/

Events & Ticketing
CalendarEventsMasterworks 20-21Special EventsConcerts for KidsFriday Dress RehearsalsPurchasing Tickets?Gift CardsSubscriptions and PromotionsGroup TicketsFAQsPicnic with the PopsCollege ClubCommunity Concerts
Orchestra
Music DirectorMusiciansConductorsStuart ChafetzAndrés LoperaRonald J. JenkinsChorusAuditionsOrchestra Auditions
About CSO
Statement on InjusticeHistoryPublic Health Update: The CoronavirusColumbus Symphony at HomeBoard of TrusteesStaffVenuesOhio TheatrePalace TheatreColumbus CommonsColumbus Museum of ArtFirst Congregational ChurchContact UsPrivacyWork With UsJob OpeningsPutting the Star in ColumbusColumbus Symphony GroveCommunity Engagement & Outreach
Education
Youth OrchestrasAuditionsMember InformationYouth OrchestraYouth Orchestra Summer PopsCadet OrchestraChamber StringsJunior StringsColumbus All City OrchestraClassroom ProgramsMindful Music MomentsYoung People's ConcertsYoung MusiciansFamily ProgramsPre Concert TalksEducator AwardsLink UpSide by SideCSO Kids KornerSymphonic Teens
News & Media
Audio/VideoIn The NewsPress ReleasesAnnual ReportBrochureBravo Program Book
Support
Corporate GivingCorporate and Foundation Partners 2018-2019Individual GivingSustaining Excellence CircleIndividual Partners 2018-2019Legacy SocietyCSO Endowment2020 Symphony GalaTribute & Memorial Giving2020 Chautauqua ExcursionVolunteer OrganizationsFriends of the Columbus SymphonyCSLPicnic with the PopsAnnual ReportPridePrincipal Musician Sponsorship ProgramBenefit Concert GivingHeroes of the Columbus Symphony
Privacy
Statement on InjusticeHistoryPublic Health Update: The CoronavirusColumbus Symphony at HomeBoard of TrusteesStaffVenuesOhio TheatrePalace TheatreColumbus CommonsColumbus Museum of ArtFirst Congregational ChurchContact UsPrivacyWork With UsJob OpeningsPutting the Star in ColumbusColumbus Symphony GroveCommunity Engagement & Outreach
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Columbus Symphony website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register for events via the purchase of individual tickets or season packages. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, Credit/Debit Card Information, (etc.)On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order tickets or season packages online and want them sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, (etc
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship tickets and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.You can register with our website if you would like to receive E-Club and email newsletters. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the E-Club registration form.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Along these same lines we do use Google analysis for tracking website statistics to monitor how the website is being used to make improvements.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured specifically to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting our offices at 614-228-9600. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 614-228-9600.
©2020 Columbus Symphony Orchestra Registered · Registered 501(c)(3). EIN: 31-6402408
